-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
--------------------------
Make the Best Words to Dear Baby
-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
制作: 飞飞
校对: 西西
cece&飞飞
-==(*^__^*)==-
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第一季 第14集
How I met your mother
Season 1 Episode 14
当你遇到某个特殊的人
when you meet someone special,
生活中会突然充满了第一次
suddenly life is full of firsts.
第一次接吻
The first kiss.
第一次共渡的夜晚
The first night together.
第一次共渡的周末
The first weekend together.
而我,这些第一次都在认识Victoria后48小时内发生了
For me,all those firsts happened  within 48 hours of meeting Victoria.
他们应该快出来了, 都周一了
They have to come out soon,it's Monday.
你觉得他们是一直在那没出来吗?
Do you think they've been in there the whole time?
我不知道该骄傲还是该担心了
I don't know whether to be proud or concerned.
也许他们根本不在里面
Maybe they're not even in there.
早上好
Good morning.
嘿,伙计们
Hey,guys.
我假装没看见好了
I'm just going to ignore that.
谢谢!
Thank you!
我希望你可以留下
I wish you could stay.
我知道, 我也想,但我得去工作, 你也有个会议
I know,me,too. But I have to go to work,and you have that meeting.
结束后打给你?
Call you afterwards?
我上班时给你发"信息"
I'll inappropriately text you during.
- 拜
- Bye.
-拜
-噢,Victoria, 你在这啊...
- Bye.
- Oh,Victoria,you're here...
- toot-a-loo!
- 拜
- Bye.
连续两天?!
Two days straight?!
哇,你房间肯定闻起来象猴子窝了现在!
Wow,your room must smell like a monkey cage!
快给出数字, Lily猜是8次,但我知道我的伙计肯定是这个两倍
Come on,give us a number. Lily guessed eight,but I know my boy got to double digits.
- 零
- 什么? 什么?
- Zero.
- What? What?
伙计们, 我们才刚认识
Guys,we just met.
而且我们都在感情上犯过急进的错误
And we both screwed up relationships in the past by jumping in too quick,
所以我们谈了下, 决定这次慢慢来
so we talked about it,and we decided to take this one slow.
- 她的主意
- 完全是她的意思!
- Her idea.
- Totally her idea!
我也不知道, 我很喜欢这女孩
But,I don't know,I'm really into this girl,
如果必须以放慢速度为代价
and if going slow is what it takes to make this happen,
那么就那样吧
I say bring it on.
三周后
three weeks later
我感觉不怎么好
I don't feel so good.
就象我的睾丸混合了摇滚和苏打
It's like my testicles mixed pop rocks and soda.
我不敢相信她让你等了整整一个月
I can't believe she's making you wait a whole month.
我可忍不了这么久
I would never put up with that.
你一辈子就和一个女人干过那事
You've only had sex with one girl in your whole life.
伤心!
Burn!
Ted, 唯一可以等足一个月的理由是:
她只差一个月满18岁
Ted,the only reason to wait a month for sex is if the girl is 17 years,11 months old.
好消息:我明天晚上不用去报道猫猫秀了
Good news: I don't have to cover the cat show tomorrow night.
谁想出去晃晃?
Who's up for hanging out?
我不行,我要和Victoria出去吃饭
Oh,I can't,I'm taking Victoria out for dinner.
不行, 明天是我们在一起9周年纪念日
No,no,we can't,it's our nine-year anniversary.
哇, 9年?
Wow,nine years?
你们的关系升入4年级了
Your relationship's a fourth grader.
- 恭喜
- 谢谢
- Congrats.
- Thanks.
我们要去Berkshires,现在正是盛产枫糖的时候
We're going to the Berkshires for the maple syrup harvest.
纽约杂志"浪漫又省钱的渡假"前五名
It's one of New York Magazine's "top five romantic getaways on a budget."
谁说性事只是兽欲?
Who says sexual can't be sensible?
似乎就只剩我们两了
Well,looks like it's going to be just you and me.
真的吗?
Really?
事实上, 我在和我的马提尼讲话
Actually,I was talking to my martini.
准备出发了?
ready to go?
那是当然
Hell,yeah.
周末躺在一张舒适的床上吃早餐
Nothing better than a weekend at a good bed and breakfast.
是啊, 早上7点起床吃早餐, 准时
Yeah. Waking up for breakfast at 7:00 A.M. Sharp.
恭维着那里的味道和他们的针织大雁
Complimenting the odors and their collection of needle-point geese.
与试图挽回婚姻的中年夫妇尴尬的谈话
Awkward conversations with middle-aged couples trying to stave off divorce.
我们最好出发了, 大概要4个小时车程
Yeah,well,we'd better get going,it's like a four-hour drive.
而且今晚还可能下雨
And it's supposed to rain tonight.
-或者我们呆在家算了
-看看电视
- Or we could just stay home.
- Maybe watch some TV.
- 订点中国餐
- 噢,四川菜!
- Order in some Chinese.
- Oh,sichuan garden!
- 我们说定了吗?
- 天,是的
- Are we really bailing?
- Hell,yeah.
太好了, 因为这袋东西是空的
Good,cause this thing's empty.
赌100块,你转过身来会令我"哇"
Hundred dollars says when you turn around,I say "wow."
Barney,这是第3次你不小心向我搭讪了
Barney,this is the third time you've hit on me by accident.
背后进攻当然会有这种风险
It's one of the many risks of the blind approach.
平常都是两人配合的,Ted在对面告诉我目标辣不辣
It's usually a two-man operation where Ted signals that the target is hot.
但Ted正在搞蕾丝
But Ted's too busy being in a lesbian relationship.
为什么不在镜子里看女孩的影像?
Why don't you just check out the girl's reflection in the bar mirror?
你不能只...哇哦!
You can't just... wow!
嘿? 怎么这么久?
Hey? What's taking so long?
我得走了
I gotta go.
别这么快,Scherbotsky
Not so fast,Scherbotsky.
我喜欢你的主意
I like the way you think.
利用镜子
That mirror thing.
简单, 优雅
Simple. Elegant.
好吧, 过期作废的提议
Okay,limited-time offer:
我需要一个兄弟,和我一起干兄弟间的事情
I need a "bro" for my bro-ings on about town.
你愿意当我的兄弟?
How would you like to be said bro?
虽然是很好的提议,不过我正在陪一个刚被人甩的朋友
Well,as tempting as that sounds,I'm hanging out with my friend who just got dumped.
她真的需要些支持...
She really needs some support...
或者陌生人的舌头伸进她喉咙
or a stranger's tongue down her throat.
那似乎很健康
That seems healthy.
好吧
All right.
我加入了
Guess I'm in.
那么...再过一周
So... one more week
就满一个月了
and it'll be a month.
真的? 你确定?
Really? Are you sure?
哇, 不知不觉的
Wow,that snuck up on me.
噢, 拜托
Oh,come on.
18岁总是姗姗来迟
The 18th can't get here fast enough.
等等, 18?
Wait,the 18th?
噢,糟糕! 我竟然会忘记!
Oh,crap! I can't believe I forgot this!
我18号那天要出城!
I'm going to be out of town on the 18th!
噢...呃
Oh. Well,um,
我们可以...等到你回来
we can just... wait until you get back.
我们既然决定了慢慢来
I mean,the whole point was not to rush into this.
是啊
Yeah.
或者我们今晚就做
Or we could do it tonight.
Amsterdam和75街路口
75th and Amsterdam.
真高兴我们决定呆在家
I'm so glad we decided to just stay home.
我理解, 你能想象如果我们去了?
Oh,I know. Can you imagine if we'd gone?
我们可能现在才刚到, 又累又烦躁
We'd be just getting there now,all tired and cranky.
做爱将变成一种义务
And yet we'd feel obligated to have sex.
为了89美元一晚的房费我们还是要做的
Yeah,for 89 bucks a night,we're doing it.
我提议我们干一杯
I would like to propose a toast.
为了我们最棒的周年纪念日
To the most awesomely mellow anniversary ever.
嗯...
Ah...
我真高兴你下周末得回父母家
I'm so glad you have to go to your parents' next weekend.
我真高兴你的室友们不在
I'm so glad your roommates are out of town.
我的天, 他们在干什么?
Oh,my god,what are they doing home?
他们以为我们走了
They think we went away.
Ted终于要得手了!
Oh,it is on for my boy,Ted.
但我们没走, 我们在浴室里
But we didn't go away,we're in the bathroom.
他们不知道这个啊
They don't know that.
我们要做的就是躲在这里等Ted把她移进卧室
All we have to do is hide out in here until Ted moves his mojo into the bedroom.
但我不想躲在这
But I don't want to hide out in here.
亲爱的, Ted等这一刻都快等疯了
Honey,Ted has been going out of his mind waiting for this.
如果我们现在出去破坏气氛,就不会继续发生了
If we go out there and spoil the mood,it's not going to happen.
我们中的一个就得去和Ted做爱
Then one of us is going to have to have sex with Ted,and...
...反正我是不干
...not gonna be me.
好, 好吧
Okay,fine.
顺便剔剔牙好了
I guess I'll actually floss.
你穿西装了!
You suited up!
要么不做
Well,I figured if I'm going to do this,
要做就做好
I'm going to do this right.
Emilio? 这位女士想要...
Emilio? The woman will have...
一杯尊尼获加, 蓝牌,不加水，一支蒙特克里斯托2号.谢谢.
I'll have a Johnnie Walker Blue,neat,and a Montecristo No. 2. Thanks.
啊, 2号...又名"鱼雷"
Ah,The No. 2,A.K.A. "The Torpedo."
卷烟工人爱把它做"Piramide."
Or,as the rollers call it,"Piramide."
我爸爸是个雪茄爱好者
这是引起他注意的唯一方法
My father was a cigar fanatic,it was the only way to get his attention.
恋父情结
Father issues.
够辣
Hot.
我知道--我离荡妇就差那么点了
I know-- I was this close to being a huge slut.
荡妇不错, 但我要一个兄弟
Slut would have been better,but I'll settle for bro.
特别是Ted和Victoria在一起不能喝酒
Especially now that Ted's with Victoria and can't drink.
因为他怀孕了
Because he's pregnant.
因为他是女的
Cause he's the girl.
得了, Ted不可能怀孕
Oh,come on,Ted can't be pregnant.
得有性生活才能怀孕
You need to have sex to get pregnant.
带劲!
What up!
来一个完美的定格!
Freeze frame high five!
我想这也许是个完美的时刻
I think this may be a perfect moment.
我希望我们能保持到永远
I wish we could hold onto it forever.
不
No.
因为这一刻的美妙就在于它很短暂
Because the beauty of a moment is that it's fleeting.
以其易逝的天性
By its very nature,
...滑过我们的手指...
it... slips through our fingers...
让这一刻更珍贵
making it that much more precious.
呃, 太糟糕了
Ugh,that is bad.
那就象, 就象高中文学杂志一样糟
That is,like,high-school- literary-magazine bad.
他们真没激情
And they're not even high.
居然这样也行
It's actually working.
是啊, 缓慢而顺畅
老天啊, 赶快搞定呀!
Yeah,smooth but slowly.
God,close the deal,already.
已经快有45分钟了, 我们可以做3次啦
It's been,like,45 minutes,we could have had sex three times by now.
是啊, 试试5次
Yeah,try five.
就是!
What up!
也许我们该出去算了
Maybe we should just go out there.
不可能!
No way!
我们现在不能出去
We can'to out there now,
他们会知道我们一直都在浴室里
they'll know that we've been sitting in the bathroom the whole time.
那就有点变态了
It'll be too weird.
好吧
Fine.
但如果我们要困在这儿...
But if we're stuck in here...
我得把音量弄大点
I'm turning up the volume. Shh. Shh.
我想要了解你
I want to know you.
比如,了解你的灵魂
Like,know your soul.
Ted, 为什么哭了?
Ted,what makes you cry?
你得把我拉住, 否则我要骂人了
Could you hold my hair back,I think I'm going to hurl.
那么,你和Ted在雪茄吧里呆过后会干什么?
So. What do you and Ted usually do after the cigar bar?
开什么玩笑?
Are you kidding?
Ted没来过
Ted's never been here.
你做的已经比他更快更高了
You've already flown higher and faster than he ever did.
还有...
Still...
什么?
what?
呃
Eh.
还有一件我们可以做的事
There is one other thing we could do.
如果你准备好
If you're up for it.
没想到现在还有激光枪战!
I had no idea laser tag still existed!
是啊, 好好享受吧,有朝一日会再次火起来的
Yeah,well,enjoy it before it becomes cool again.
我认为两个月以后
I give it two months.
噢，我信你, 这太棒了!
Oh,I believe it,this is awesome!
好了, 跟着我, 低点
Okay,follow my lead,stay low,
不要低估12岁的家伙..
and never underestimate a 12-year-old with a...
Scherbotsky, 你得专心点!
Scherbotsky,you gotta focus!
你刚救了我一命, 是吗?
You just saved my life,didn't you?
等会再谢我
Thank me later.
继续行动.
Let's keep moving.
这些小王八蛋无处不在
These little bastards are everywhere
他只是凝视着她的眼睛
he's just staring into her eyes.
我不知道,我们以前比Ted和Victoria更恶心
I don't know,we used to be even more nauseatingly into each other than Ted and Victoria.
- 现在看看我们
- 是啊...
- Now look at us.
- Yeah...
现在我们只会嘲笑人们那样
now we just make fun of people like that.
这是生命的轮回
It's the circle of life.
别, 我认真的, Marshall
No,I'm serious,Marshall.
我是说, 我们都提不起兴趣出门
I mean,we couldn't even get it up to go on our big trip.
然后现在我们困在浴室里庆祝我们的纪念日
And now we're celebrating our anniversary stuck in a bathroom.
拿我们跟Ted和Victoria比不公平
Well,it's not fair to compare us to Ted and Victoria.
这是他们的第一次
This is their first time.
是, 但是我们还是可以多浪漫点
Yeah,but we could still have some more romance.
现在, 你就说,"想做吗?"
然后我说, "好啊"
Now,you just say,"want to do it?" And I say,"yeah."
- 想...
- 不!
- Want to...
- no!
也许我们只是用光了第一次
Maybe we're just out of firsts.
好象他们要迎来他们的第一次了
Looks like they're about to have theirs.
我们可以去卧室吗?
Should we take this to the bedroom?
好! 好!
Yes! Yes!
好的
Yes.
好! 好!
Yes! Yes!
不 不要, 别接!
No. No,don't answer it!
你可以接它
you could answer it.
我们有整晚
We have all night.
你要接吗? 他接了电话!
You're answering it? He's answering it!
别! 上了她! 现在就上了她!
No! Do her! Do her now!
当然, 祝你好运
Sure. Good luck with that.
抱歉
Sorry about that.
再来点酒怎么样?
How about a little more wine?
- 我再去拿一瓶
- 谢谢
- I'll get another bottle.
- Thank you.
我也要喝
I need a drink.
这里有止咳糖浆吗?
Do we have any cough syrup in here?
嘘...
Shh...
伏击! 伏击!伏击!
Ambush! Ambush! Ambush!
噢, 天, 我们被这些小鬼包围了
oh,god. These brats have us completely surrounded.
我数出9人,也许10人
I counted nine,maybe ten.
我会掩护, 你跑过去
I'll lay down some cover fire,you make a run for it.
不, 绝不放弃一名战友
No. Leave no man behind.
我们要么全出去, 要么都别出去
Either we all get out of here or no one does.
- 但我...
- 别逞英雄, Scherbotsky
- But I...
- don't be a hero,Scherbotsky.
另一边见
See you on the other side.
该死
damn.
想来点酥软的椒盐卷饼吗?
Want to go get a soft pretzel?
- 耶
- 好吧
- Yeah.
- All right.
Marshall, 我们怎么了?
Marshall,what happened to us?
我们曾凝视对方整晚
We used to just stare into each other's eyes all night long.
我们失去这些了吗?
Have we lost that?
也许
Maybe.
但我想我刚刚找回来了
But I think I just found it.
就在这
Right here.
宝贝, 我要给你燃烧的激情
Baby,I'm giving you sexy smolding
只用一对暗示的眼神
with just a hint of crazy eyes.
噢
Oh.
好吧, 准备好接受我的性感透视光
Okay,well,get ready for my sex-ray vision.
你有记得把干洗的衣服拿回来吗?
Did you remember to pick up the dry cleaning?
- 噢, 真该死
- 没事我们可以这样
- Oh,damn it.
- It's all right. We can do this.
我们握着手
Let's just hold hands.
感觉还不错..
This is nice. .
你喜欢这小动作
You love that move.
这才是经典的Marshall
It's a classic Marshall.
好吧, 我们就只能这样了
All right,we totally suck at this.
我们真的, 真的得出去
We really,really need to get out of here.
嗯, 我们不能
Well,we can't.
宝贝, 有件事我必需得做,但我如果在你面前做
Baby,there's something I have to do,and if I do it in front of you,
会从本质上改变我们的关系
it'll change the entire nature of our relationship.
那是什么?
What is it?
我要尿尿
I have to pee.
- 太糟了
- 是啊
- This is bad.
- Yeah.
我们9年都没有在对方面前尿尿过
We've gone nine years without peeing in front of each other.
你一直以为时间有得是
You always think there'll be more time.
看看我们
Look at us.
我们完全是一对年老的夫妻了
We're basically an old married couple,
而且我们甚至还没结婚
and we're not even married yet.
我们的浪漫火焰正在消逝
The flame of our romance is flickering,
如果我朝上面尿尿,它也许就会永远熄灭了
and if I pee all over it,it might go out forever.
你觉得你能憋多久?
How much longer do you think you can hold it?
在他们量变到质变的漫长过程中
我喝了不少mountain dew
I drank a big gulp of Mountain Dew during that Quantum Leap marathon.
噢, 坏了
Oh,boy.
玩激光枪战真的让我回到了从前
Playing laser tag really takes me back.
你知道我很想念什么游戏吗?
军舰棋
you know what game I really miss? Battleship.
- 我从来没输过一次
- 我也是
- I've never lost a game.
- Neither have I.
- 我是靠作弊
- 噢, 对, 我也是
- Of course I cheat.
- Oh,yeah,me,too.
我都是把航母折起来做成L形
The trick is to bend the aircraft carrier so it makes an L.
啊, 我通常是把棋子摞起来
Ah. I always just stacked the ships on top of each other.
不错, 我们可以来一个作弊招数大比拼
Nice. You know,we should have a cheaters grudge match.
我觉得我还是有一定的...
I think I still have a...
注意, 目标出现, 点歌机旁的美女
hello. Target acquired. Hottie by the jukebox.
噢, 好眼光Scherbotsky
Oh,good eye, Scherbotsky.
我给你找了个两点钟方向, 穿蓝色衬衫
I got someone for you. Two o'clock,blue shirt.
那是个女的
That's a woman.
噢, 我错了
Oh,my mistake.
或者...没错?
Or... is it?
我们专心对付你的目标吧
Let's just focus on your target.
好
Right.
这个我来
I got this one.
老天, 我喜欢你的仔裤
Oh,my god. I love your jeans.
好吧, 这里是女同性恋酒吧吗?
Okay. Is this a lesbian bar?
因为那个穿蓝色衬衫的女的刚刚...
Because that girl with the blue shirt just...
噢, 不是, 我只对男人有兴趣
oh,no. I am all about the dudes.
不过今晚真的挑不到什么好的
Although pickings are pretty slim tonight.
唯一一个看上眼的金发西服小子,还在玩冷若冰霜
Only hot guy here is blondie in the suit,and he's playing hard to get.
是吗? 他现在可是盯着我在
really? Cause he's totally vibing me right now.
一定是仔裤
must be the jeans.
不过, 仔裤就只能帮你这么多了
Well,jeans will only get you so far.
我要和他一起回家
I'm going home with him.
我们走着瞧
we'll see about that.
我的上帝, 我讨厌Ted
我太讨厌他了!
oh,my god,I hate Ted.
I hate him so much.
宝贝, 你为什么不干脆尿了?
Baby,why don't you just go?
无数的夫妻都在对方面前尿过尿
Tons of other couples have peed in front of each other.
不, 但我们没有,因为我想保持一定的神秘
No,but we haven't,because I want to keep some of the mystery alive.
你有在我面前放过屁
Well,you have farted in front of me.
是的, 但我都以咳嗽掩护了
Yes,but I always cover it with a cough.
你一直都是
You always do.
- 嘿
- Hey.
我们走吧, 去什么别的地方
Let's get out of here. Let's go somewhere else.
怎么了?
What happened?
有时候我会想玩玩七擒七纵
You sometimes like to do a little catch and release.
但为什么?
But why?
绝不留下战友
Leave no man behind.
要么我们都找到目标, 要么都别
Either we all score or no one scores.
不错
Right on.
嘿,你想玩军舰棋吗?
Hey,you want to go play battleship?
中!
Hit!
Ted
Ted,
我再也等不急了
I can't wait any longer.
我们该去卧室吗?
Should we move to the bedroom?
没时间过去了
There's no time for that.
他们可以吸对方的手指整个小时
They can suck on each other's fingers for an hour,
却没时间走两步去卧室?
but there's no time to take two steps to the bedroom?
宝贝, 我再也憋不住了
Baby,I can't hold it in any longer.
到时候了
It's time.
我知道
I know.
我爱你, Marshall
I love you,Marshall.
我爱你, Lily
I love you,Lily.
来吧
here we go.
知道吗, Barney,我今晚当你兄弟很愉快
You know,Barney,I had a surprisingly good time bro-ing out tonight.
嗯, 你是个好兄弟
Well,you make a good bro.
你比Ted更Ted
you're a better Ted than Ted.
嘿, 事实上
Hey,in fact,
你的表现令你得到了Marshall的单身派对的邀请
you have just earned yourself an invite to Marshall's bachelor party.
你甚至不用带蛋糕去
And you don't even have to come out of the cake.
谢谢
Thanks.
还有, 呃, 谢谢你今晚陪我
And,um,thanks for sticking around tonight.
希望你准备好来一场高难度的军舰大战
I hope you're ready for some hard-core battleship.
来吧, 小伙子们
Come on,boys.
高难度?
Hardcore?
玩的就是高难度
（Hardcore也指A片的一个类别）
That's the only way I play.
我找到了, 你准备好...
I found it. Are you ready to...
你在干什么?
what the hell are you doing?
换上出生时的装束
I'm birthday suiting up.
抱歉, 你想帮我脱光吗?
I'm sorry,did you want to undress me?
不! 我认为我们只是象朋友一样出去玩
No! I thought we were just hanging out as friends.
噢, 拜托, 你整晚都在向我投怀送抱
Oh,come on,you have been throwing yourself at me all night.
什么?! 我正好相反!我把别的女孩投进你的怀抱
What?! I did the opposite! I threw some other girl at you.
你邀请我到你公寓来玩"军舰棋"
You invited me up to your apartment to "play battleship."
这不是国际公认的做爱的暗语?
Is that not an internationally recognized term for sex?
不是
No.
太好了
Great.
我希望你开心
I hope you're happy.
你击沉了我的军舰
You sunk my battleship.
我还好
I'm okay.
你呢?
You okay?
我感觉还是一样
I feel the same.
不过, 有一点点异样
And yet,strangely different.
我为我的膀胱高兴
I'm happy for my bladder,
也为我们而难过
yet sad for us.
你必须得那样, 甜心...
You had to do it,sweetie...
为了Ted
for Ted.
还有,嘿，看，至少我们想呆多久都可以了
And,hey,look,at least now we can stay in here as long as it takes.
是啊, 只能牺牲我们的关系
Yeah, I guess our relationship had to take a hit
让外面的新一对可以绽放
so a new one out there could blossom.
噢, 糟糕!
Oh,crap!
他们一定听到了
They must have heard that.
好了，我猜我们可以出去了
Well,I guess we can come out now.
我不敢相信, 他们走了
I don't believe it. They're gone.
很好, 因为我也得去厕所
Good. Cause I got to take a whiz.
好了, 我和你, 这简直是疯了
Okay,you and me,that's insane.
如果你有想一秒钟...
If you even thought about it for one second...
但我想了3秒钟, 这很合情理
but I have thought about it for three seconds,and it makes a lot of sense.
我们都认为婚姻承诺是狗屁
We both think the marriage commitment thing's a drag.
我们都想要舒适和开心的东西
We both want something casual and fun.
还有我们显然相处的很好
And we clearly get along really well.
哇, 这听起来是很合理
Wow,that actually did make a lot of sense.
但Ted会怎么想?
But what about Ted?
我给Ted打了招呼了
I checked with Ted.
Ted, 现在你和Victoria进展的这么顺利
Ted,so now that things with you and Victoria are going pretty well,
我猜以前你喜欢的女孩已经不重要了
是吗?
I assume you're over all the girls you were into before,right?
你沉默我就当是了,那么我要和某人约会
I take your silence as a yes,so say I were to hook up with someone,
我指Robin,你不会介意吧, 是不?
say Robin,you'd be cool with that,right?
当然, 祝你好运
sure. Good luck with that.
哈! 完全是在祝福我们
Ha! Totally gave us his blessing.
真的吗?
Really?
真的
Really.
那么Ted完全不在意你对我采取行动?
So Ted didn't care that you wanted to make a move on me?
完全不在意
Didn't care at all.
噢. 噢...
Oh. Oh...
什么?
what?
你喜欢Ted
You like Ted.
- 我没说我喜欢Ted
- 你喜欢Ted
- I didn't say I liked Ted
- you like Ted.
哇, 这真震撼
Wow. This is huge.
Barney, 我不喜欢Ted
Barney,I don't like Ted.
他朝前走了, 我也真心高兴...
He's moved on,and I'm really happy for...
是啊是啊,我们要玩军舰棋还是怎样?
yeah,yeah. Look,are we gonna play battleship or what?
你不会去告诉他的, 是不?
You're not gonna tell him,are you?
不会
No.
这是兄弟原则
That's the bro code.
一个兄弟不会告诉另一个兄弟第三个兄弟喜欢他
A bro doesn't tell a mutual bro that a third bro has a crush on him.
就像第三个兄弟不会告诉另一个兄弟
Just like the third bro doesn't tell the mutual br
最初的兄弟在她面前剥了光猪
that the original bro went bare pickle in front of her.
这是兄弟为了兄弟
It's quid pro bro.
- A7
- 没中
- A7.
- Miss.
当然
Of course.
好了，我们还有一个没有在对方面前那样
Well,we still have one frontier left.
还是赛点
Still got the deuce.
这不能让我感觉更好
Not making me feel better.
嗯，这是一个"第一次"
Well,it certainly was a first.
这就是, 不是吗?
It was,wasn't it?
我们还有第一次
We still have firsts.
当然我们有
Of course we do.
还有你知道吗, 我感觉和你走的更近了
And you know what,I actually feel closer to you now.
我想去了解你，比如, 了解你的灵魂
I want to know you. Like,know your soul.
Marshall, 为什么哭了?
Marshall,what makes you cry?
这一刻是短暂的
This moment is fleeting
因为它被下一刻追逐
because it's being chased by another moment.
噢, 比抓胸部还有效
Oh,just grab my boob already.
拜托, 伙计们, 到房间去
Come on,guys,get a room.
--------------------------
cece&飞飞字幕组倾情奉献
组长：cece
组员：cece&飞飞
--------------------------
-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
制作: 飞飞
校对: 西西
-==cece&飞飞==-
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第一季 第14集 结束
How I met your mother
Season 1 Episode 14